This is the new night time. I dare you to wear this silver retro design now, right?
Cute face, isn't it? Nighttime and idols!
Yes, I know, I don't have much fun to talk about, but this is the end of the show. Thank you very much.
Now, please listen to the announcement from Mr. Hori.
Yes, it will be performed at Tokyo Kinema Club on Wednesday, September 6,
I will be performing in "Tokyo Yakan Land Vol. 3: Rose of Uguisudani" at Tokyo Kinema Club on Wednesday, September 6.
There are many performers here, and Haruna-san, formerly of Takoyaki de Iimono, will be next to me,
Yes, that's right. What do you think? Have you talked about this or something in particular? Yes, I have. There is also Haruna, who is more glorious and beautiful.
How is it? Have you talked about this in particular?
Yes, we haven't.
We haven't met yet.
It's been a long time since we've seen each other.
I see.
So you're looking forward to it?
I'm looking forward to it.
Are there any members who are calling?
I'm glad to see that all of them are pretty good friends of mine.
Yuzuki-chan is also a member of the same purple group, and we have become good friends,
Hajimari-Yan.
Good luck to Hajimai-san.
I think he will probably come with great energy.
Rumpin is there too.
Here's the next announcement.
Yes, every Saturday morning from 6:30 to 8:00 a.m.
ABC TV Ohayo Asahi Saturday.
I'm a reporter.
This is local to the Kansai region.
If you are in Kansai, please watch it!
If you are not from Kansai, please watch it when you come to Kansai.
I hope you will watch it when you come to Kansai.
Please take a look at the other announcement.
We are now broadcasting a regular monthly program, Obanzai Coo-chan, on Cookpad Live.
September is almost here, though it may have just ended soon,
I'm allowed to do it every month, so I'll announce it on SNS and other places, so please
There will be viewing, so please come and play!
Please come and visit us!Please.
What kind of show is this?
It's a show where I make an obanzai-style rice dish that goes well with sake.
And drink it while eating it.
So it's about drinking at the end?
Yes, because I like to drink.
So you did this for me.
We arranged the drinks and compared them.
We also had guests participate in a game, and if they got it right, they got a cookie.
If they answered correctly, they got cookies.
I drew the illustrations.
There are various points to be scored, so please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please.
Yes, I'm having fun with everyone. It's great!
Now then, as I mentioned at the end of the show, Yakkan-kun will be giving away some tea to cheer you up... sorry, it's not alcohol, but it is tea.
Tea!
Today's tea is a blend of herbs to soothe your throat!
It smells so good!
Please try it!
Wow!
The only reaction I got was, "Wow.
It's so easy to drink.
It's easy to drink, even though it's an herbal tea.
It's very refreshing and makes my throat feel better.
Thank you very much.
And last but not least...
Cute, but not too cute.
Please give us your closing remarks in a cute way.
Tokyo Night Land Vol. 3
Roses in a greenish brown mound
Come visit us!
This program is
Extremist Gorilla-chan
Takahina-san
Toshikazu-san, Aggressive Gorilla-chan Takahiro-san
Toshikazu-sanToshikazu
Satomi-san
Courtesy of Mr. Akin, who becomes a toshiko ukiyo when he drinks sake!
Thank you all for your contributions.
Thank you very much for your contribution!
See you again!